Tyler Mire

Software Developer and IT specialist

Phone: (503) 875-8766

Email: <u>tyler.j.mire@gmail.com</u>

Personal Site: Tylerjmire.com

Github: https://github.com/DomesticatedLumberjack

SKILLS

Determined individual with a passion for technology. Wealth of experience with various types of hardware and software configurations for computing including: desktops and laptops running both Windows and GNU/Linux, Windows and GNU/Linux servers, software development in various OOP languages, javascript/typescript, and desktop/laptop computer hardware.

EXPERIENCE

Carisbrook - Wilsonville, OR - Project Support Associate / Help Desk Technician June 2019 - January 2020

- Tackled project tickets by making sure hardware/software upgrades were completed successfully.
- Handled incoming calls and assisted clients with technical support issues.

TekSystems - Beaverton, OR - Contractor

September 2017 - June 2019

- Best Buy: Performed store health checks by ensuring that various tasks were completed around the store and ensuring that they were up to store standards.
- Adidas: Worked at the Adidas campus to assist with the setup of desktop hardware and networking infrastructure.

Coding With Kids - Portland, OR - *Instructor*

May 2018 - September 2018

- Taught at various schools in the Portland and Beaverton school districts teaching elementary students the basics of programming with Scratch.
- Managed classrooms of up to 20 students and made sure that they stayed on task.

EDUCATION

Portland Community College, Portland - Associate of Science

Fall 2015 - Spring 2019

Spent the majority of my time at PCC studying computer science, mathematics, and physics.